https://itsenclosures.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyYou are here: Home / About Us / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
ITSENCLOSURES (“us”, “we”, or “our”) designs and builds the most durable computer, electronic and display enclosures solutions on the market.  ITSENCLOSURES, for its website and registered Members, created this in order to ensure the confidence of our Members, website visitors and partners (“you” or “your”), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. Our policy is subject to change over time, so please review it periodically for any updates.
Types of Information Collected
Traffic Data Collected. In addition to the registration information you provide to us to become a Member, we automatically track and collect information when you visit the Website, including your: (a) IP address; (b) domain server; (c) type of computer; and (d) type of web browser (collectively, “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes and for improving your experience on the Website. We also use “cookies” to customize content specific to your interests, to ensure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, and to lead a registered Member directly to a login screen. Cookies are small pieces of information that a website places on your computer’s hard drive for tracking purposes. Like most websites, we use cookie information to improve the efficiency of customer service, allow Members to easily change addresses, and to add or cancel memberships by automatically verifying that you are a Member. We also use cookies to enhance the Website’s content by compiling aggregate information about what specific sections and pages that users visit. Cookies may also be placed by third parties when you click-through from the Website to an advertisement or otherwise link to a website maintained by a third party. Though we may encourage third parties to adhere to appropriate privacy practices, we are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties and you should review them carefully before providing any personally identifying information to such parties.
Personally Identifying Information
In order for you to access certain Member services and to purchase products that we offer on the Website, we require you to provide us with information that personally identifies you (collectively, “Personal Information”). Personal Information may include: (i) your name, mailing and e-mail addresses (collectively, “Contact Data”); (ii) your account or credit card number (collectively, “Financial Data”); and (iii) your zip code, age and income (collectively, “Demographic Data”). If you communicate with us by email, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, if any, complete online forms, surveys, contest entries, or the like, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.
Uses of Information Collected
We use Contact Data to send you information about our company, our products and services, promotional material from our partners, or to contact you when necessary concerning your membership. We use your Financial Data to verify your qualifications and to bill you for products and services. We use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website by displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences.
Sharing of Personal Information
We use Contact Data to send you information about our company, our products and services, promotional material, or to contact you. We use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website by displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences. We DO NOT share Contact Data or Financial Data of Members with other companies or persons. However, we have no control over any Personal Information you provide to a third party whose website is linked to the Website or to other third parties.
User Choice Regarding Collection, Use and Distribution of Personal Information
If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us, you may (a) select the appropriate “opt-out” option on the materials or information sent; (b) contact us at info@itsenclosures.com; or (c) hit the “Reply” button on any email from us, and inform us that you do not wish to receive any information or promotional materials.
Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information
Except as otherwise provided in this, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; (c) enforce our Terms of Service; or (d) protect someone’s safety. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers of our web host that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.
Other Limits to Your Privacy
The Website contains links to other websites. Please understand that any information that is disclosed by you directly or indirectly in such areas becomes public information that cannot be controlled by us. We have no control over its use and dissemination and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any Personal Information.
Modifications to Privacy Policy
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to update or otherwise modify this by posting such update or other modification at the page on the Website. Any update or other modification shall be effective immediately upon such posting. Accordingly, we encourage you to review this periodically to determine if it has been modified.
Privacy Policy
ITSENCLOSURES (“us”, “we”, or “our”) designs and builds the most durable computer, electronic and display enclosures solutions on the market.  ITSENCLOSURES, for its website and registered Members, created this in order to ensure the confidence of our Members, website visitors and partners (“you” or “your”), and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. Our policy is subject to change over time, so please review it periodically for any updates.
Types of Information Collected
Traffic Data Collected. In addition to the registration information you provide to us to become a Member, we automatically track and collect information when you visit the Website, including your: (a) IP address; (b) domain server; (c) type of computer; and (d) type of web browser (collectively, “Traffic Data”). Traffic Data is information that does not personally identify you but is helpful for marketing purposes and for improving your experience on the Website. We also use “cookies” to customize content specific to your interests, to ensure that you do not see the same advertisement repeatedly, and to lead a registered Member directly to a login screen. Cookies are small pieces of information that a website places on your computer’s hard drive for tracking purposes. Like most websites, we use cookie information to improve the efficiency of customer service, allow Members to easily change addresses, and to add or cancel memberships by automatically verifying that you are a Member. We also use cookies to enhance the Website’s content by compiling aggregate information about what specific sections and pages that users visit. Cookies may also be placed by third parties when you click-through from the Website to an advertisement or otherwise link to a website maintained by a third party. Though we may encourage third parties to adhere to appropriate privacy practices, we are not responsible for the policies or practices of third parties and you should review them carefully before providing any personally identifying information to such parties.
Personally Identifying Information
In order for you to access certain Member services and to purchase products that we offer on the Website, we require you to provide us with information that personally identifies you (collectively, “Personal Information”). Personal Information may include: (i) your name, mailing and e-mail addresses (collectively, “Contact Data”); (ii) your account or credit card number (collectively, “Financial Data”); and (iii) your zip code, age and income (collectively, “Demographic Data”). If you communicate with us by email, post messages to any of our chat groups, bulletin boards, or forums, if any, complete online forms, surveys, contest entries, or the like, any information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information.
Uses of Information Collected
We use Contact Data to send you information about our company, our products and services, promotional material from our partners, or to contact you when necessary concerning your membership. We use your Financial Data to verify your qualifications and to bill you for products and services. We use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website by displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences.
Sharing of Personal Information
We use Contact Data to send you information about our company, our products and services, promotional material, or to contact you. We use your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Website by displaying content that we think you might be interested in and according to your preferences. We DO NOT share Contact Data or Financial Data of Members with other companies or persons. However, we have no control over any Personal Information you provide to a third party whose website is linked to the Website or to other third parties.
User Choice Regarding Collection, Use and Distribution of Personal Information
If you do not wish to receive information and promotional material from us, you may (a) select the appropriate “opt-out” option on the materials or information sent; (b) contact us at info@itsenclosures.com; or (c) hit the “Reply” button on any email from us, and inform us that you do not wish to receive any information or promotional materials.
Confidentiality and Security of Personal Information
Except as otherwise provided in this, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process; (b) protect our rights or property; (c) enforce our Terms of Service; or (d) protect someone’s safety. Your Personal Information is stored on secure servers of our web host that are not accessible by third parties. We provide you with the capability to transmit your Personal Information via secured and encrypted channels if you use a similarly equipped web browser.
Other Limits to Your Privacy
The Website contains links to other websites. Please understand that any information that is disclosed by you directly or indirectly in such areas becomes public information that cannot be controlled by us. We have no control over its use and dissemination and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any Personal Information.
Modifications to Privacy Policy
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to update or otherwise modify this by posting such update or other modification at the page on the Website. Any update or other modification shall be effective immediately upon such posting. Accordingly, we encourage you to review this periodically to determine if it has been modified.
ITSENCLOSURES
Computer Enclosures
Printer Enclosures
Digital Menu Boards
LCD Enclosures
Rack Enclosures
Monitor Enclosures
CONNECT
The toughest enclosures on the planet and always Made in the USA!
Scroll to top
Request Quote
Product ID:
Product Title:
Product Colors:
Please check the box if you would like to sign-up for our marketing emails. Thanks!
